Dale Holstein

I am a full stack web developer who discovered an interest in technology at a young age when I was introduced to a Nintendo. Many years later I stumbled upon programming and discovered a passion for solving problems with code. Over the past couple of years I have been working on various projects and honing my skills as a developer. Below you can find some of my completed projects.

Charlotte, NC
(704) 390-8893
dholstein30@gmail.com
github.com/Zarnerz
https://zarnerz.github.io/Port
folio-Grid/

PROJECTS

Detail Devil - Lead Backend Developer

http://thedetaildevil.herokuapp.com/

Car Detail Booking Application built with Handlebars, Node, React, Express, MongoDB and Bcrypt.

New York Times React - Sole Developer

https://nytreact-dale.herokuapp.com/

React Application that returns articles from the New York Time's API. Built using MongoDB, Express, React, Node, Axios, and Mongoose.

Friday Nite Fights - Sole Developer

https://fridaynitefights.herokuapp.com/

Official website for Friday Nite Fights weekly Fortnite tournaments. Built using HTML, SASS, Node, Express, MongoDB, and Mongoose.

EXPERIENCE

Autobell Car Wash, Indian Trail, NC — *Crew Member*

October 2015 - PRESENT

Boone County Schools, Madison, WV—Substitute Teacher

April 2015 - September 2015

Cooperated with administration and students to get a struggling program back on track, facilitated learning by establishing a relationship with students and organizing classroom resources and environment, developed a system that simulated a real world workplace which resulted in a 95% pass rate (up from 60% of students passing before I arrived).

Bluegreen Vacations, St. Augustine, FL— *Administrative Assistant*

May 2014 - December 2014

Supported directors of marketing and sales in all functions vital to running an administrative office efficiently, maintained accurate and confidential data of clients, scheduled sales appointments, and resolved any problems or questions that guests had.

SKILLS

HTML & CSS (SASS)

JavaScript & AJAX

Node & Express

SQL & MongoDB

React

Git

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Charlotte – JavaScript Full Stack Web Development: Curriculum included: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Express, React, SQL, MongoDB & Git.

Marshall University -Bachelor of Arts: History : Magna Cum Laude